Tinúviel Papers, 1988-2005
Sophia Smith Collection
Tinuviel papers
1988-2005
Tinúviel, 1963-
MS 518
16 boxes (7 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Music producer; Feminist; Peace activist; Artist; co-founder of the groundbreaking record label Kill Rock Stars, in Olympia, WA, and later the all-girl record label, Villa Villakula. The papers include materials pertaining to Tinúviel's feminist music recording and distribution company; recordings by girls and women; newspapers, magazines, zines, correspondence, and a small amount of writings by Tinúviel.
Tinúviel (her full name) was born July 23, 1963 in Los Angeles, California, to Irene Anna Bogdanovs (an immigrant from Latvia who came to the U.S. in 1950) and Richard Joseph Sampson from Los Angeles. A few years later her family moved to Philadelphia, then to Hiroshima, Japan, then Rochester, Minnesota, then Newton, Massachusetts, where she lived until the age of 18 (approximately three years in each location due to her father's schooling and military service). She was a "visiting student" at Smith College in the 1980s, and in 1989, moved to the west coast to finish school at Evergreen State College in Olympia, Washington.
In Olympia, she and her friend Slim Moon co-founded the groundbreaking record label Kill Rock Stars, characterized as "open, experimental, full of Riot Grrrls" with a strong feminist voice (from interview for Wire radio program, "The art of dissent," July 2005). A few years later she moved back East where she founded the all-girl record label, Villa Villakula. Tinúviel currently defines herself as a peace activist and political artist, incorporating anti-war messages in much of her artwork.
The Tinúviel Papers consist of 7 linear feet and primarily document her work with Olympia, Washington independent record label, Kill Rock Stars as well as her own Boston-based feminist recording and distribution company, Villa Villakula. Types of material include artwork, posters, flyers, correspondence, recordings (including audiotapes, compact disks, and phonograph records), news clippings, subject files, "Girl zines" (with inserts), writings, financial records, and memorabilia. The papers are arranged in five series:
I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL
II. CORRESPONDENCE
III. RECORD LABELS
IV. SUBJECT FILES
V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
OVERSIZE MATERIALS
The bulk of the papers date from 1988 to 2000 and focus on promotion, marketing, production and distribution of Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula recording artists. The correspondence with artists on the Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula labels offers an in-depth look at the life of working indie musicians in the 1990s. Tinúviel's personal notes, correspondence and financial records document her passion for music, dedication to promoting feminist musicians, and the emotional and financial struggle of running a record label and promoting bands as an occupation. In addition, the papers document an influential subculture firmly rooted in a "do-it-yourself" ethic.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS 1988-2000, .75 linear feet
  This series provides an overview of Tinúviel's life and includes financial and legal information, personal correspondence, press, writing for zines, and original artwork.
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE 1992-2001, 1 linear foot
  This series includes personal and professional correspondence, arranged alphabetically. Most notable are letters to and from prominent musicians, rock journalists, and writers. The correspondence details the experiences of women in music business in the 1990s, the life of touring musicians, the financial challenges of working in the music industry, and how the Riot Grrrl movement was perceived and received by the public and rock journalists.
- SERIES III. RECORD LABELS 1990-1998, 2.25 linear feet
  Included in this series are materials related to record labels Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula, as well as some general information about record production, manufacture, and packaging. Materials related to both Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula include contracts, tour riders, correspondence, newsletters, and album art. The more extensive Villa Villakula materials also contain press and publicity materials such as clippings, reviews, and contact and mailing lists; as well as financial records, such as invoices, receipts, and correspondence related to releases and distribution.
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES 1991-2005, 1.25 linear feet
  This series contains clippings, publications about the music business and women in music, and underground and mainstream magazine coverage of Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula labels and recording artists.
- SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS 1991-1998, 1 linear foot
  This series includes LP and EP vinyl discs, compact discs, and audiocassette tapes released or distributed by Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula. They are arranged by format.
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, .75 linear feet
  This series includes oversize artwork, posters, newsletters, magazines, and news clippings related to Tinúviel's art and record labels.
The papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions.
Periodic additions are expected and may not be reflected in this record.
Tinúviel began donating her Papers to the Sophia Smith Collection in 2005.
Feminism and music -- United States -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Women musicians -- United States -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Lesbian feminism -- United States -- History -- Sources; Women artists -- Biography -- Sources; Artists -- Political activity -- United States; Teenage girls in popular culture; Underground press publications -- United States; Women -- Rock music; Young women -- Social life and customs -- United States; Tinúviel, 1963-; Female friendships and lesbians; Women of rock; Women in rock; Zines; Riot grrrl movement
Related materials can be found in the Sophia Smith Collection in the Girl Zines Collection, Music Collection, and the Women of Rock Oral History Project.
Tinuviel's substantial collection of girl zines have been moved to the Girl Zines Collection in the Sophia Smith Collection.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND WRITING
  - Financial, 1995-99 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - News clippings, 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Art and writing (Box 1)
    [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS]
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Writing for zines and other publications, 1988-96 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Personal writings and correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Rock She Wrote: Women Write About Rock, Pop, and Rap edited by Evelyn McDonnell and Ann Powers
      - Essay and cover art, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Cover templates, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Astrology charts, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Girl Zines
    - Correspondence
      - 1992-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
      - Loose pages and proofs, 1991-93, undated (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - A-C, 1994-97 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appleton, Robert, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Azzerad, Michael, 1994-95 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - B., Andrea, 1993-96 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - B., Gretchen, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Carangelo, Audrey, 1995-98 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - D-L, 1992-98 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dame Darcy, 1996, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Jaina, 1996-98 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Evans, Michael, 1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fox, Sue P., 1993-94 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gaar, Gillian, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Gourfain, Noon, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gomez, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hanna, Kathleen, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Holiday cards, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Irini, 1993-95 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Lombardi, Laura, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - M-Q, 1993-97 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Madigan (band), 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Marcus, Griel, 1993-95 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - McDonnell, Evelyn, 1994-95 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Moon, Slim, 1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Nagle, Colleen, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Neuman, Molly, 1992, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - R, 1995-98 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rogers, Jennifer, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - S, 1993-97 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sandra (Elektra Records), 1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Jen, 1994-95 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Snail, Azalia, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - T-Z, 1993-99 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Tucker, Corin, 1994-97 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Wolfe, Allison, 1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Wood, Jen, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Phone numbers and business cards, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Post cards, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Greeting cards and letters, 1993-2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- SERIES III. RECORD LABELS
  - Kill Rock Stars
    - Contracts, tour riders and related correspondence, 1993-94 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Promotional materials, news clippings, and reviews, 1992-93 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Rebel Girl" pocket folder: writing, correspondence, publications, 1992-94 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Newsletter layouts, 1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Bratmobile newsletter, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter layout, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Press release, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Artwork and layouts for newsletter, catalogues, etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Rock Stars Kill" compilation: layout and artwork, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bikini Kill "Pussy Whipped," layout, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Press kits and photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Fliers, club schedules, set lists, and related materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Art Forum articles re women's art, 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Penny Arcade "Bitch! Dyke! Fag Hag! Whore!" performance piece: program notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Radio, press and venue contacts, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous discography, artwork, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "The Play," Kill Rock Stars, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Mail order catalogue, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Villa Villakula
    - Bands and Artists
      - Tattle Tale, Madigan, Bonfire Madigan, 1997-98 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Victory at Sea, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - The Pendulum Floors, 1996-97 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Fresh Fish, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Un Cuerpo Exquisito
        - "Te Quiere, Tu Amante Bilingue," 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - "Universidad De Culus Expertos," 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Laura McFarlane/ Ninety-nine, 1996-97 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Sleater Kinney, 1996-98 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Dame Darcy, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Jen Wood, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ruby Falls, "The Spirit Is Winning," 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - No Neck Blues, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Bonfire Madigan, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Pagan Holiday (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Press kits, 1993-94 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Releases
      - "Stargirl," EP, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence re: The Boredoms and VVK compilation album (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - "Move into Villa Villakula": album art, press, publicity, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
      - Mail order catalogues, 1994-97 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Ad graphics (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Press and Publicity
      - About label and website: notes, drafts, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - "Girl Label Directory" by Tinúviel: information and correspondence, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - SWIM Notes: The Strong Women in Music Newsletter and related writings, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Radio contacts, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Press contacts, 1993-97 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Flyers, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Label catalogues and original artwork, 1996-97 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Ads and original artwork, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Mailing and phone lists (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Magazine and press contacts, 1996, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Advertising information and contacts, 1995-96, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Label publicity and press, 1994-97 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Riot Grrrl Convention, Boston MA, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Loud Music Fest, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8-10)
    - Financial
      - Accounts payable: invoices and correspondence, 1995-97 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Distribution: receipts and correspondence, 1996-98 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Surefire Distribution
      - Paid receipts, 1996-98 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
      - Invoices, 1997-99 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Printing information, 1988-95 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Vinyl pressing information, 1996-98 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General cassette and compact disc production, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
  - Music and women in music, general (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous catalogues (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Music magazines
    - 8-Track Mind, #83, 98 1994, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Hexbender: an Aggressive Music Journal, summer 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kitty Magik, Issue 102004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Magnet, Real Music Alternatives, 1997-98 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mangajin, Japanese Pop Culture and Language Learning, "Pop Music in Japan," Issue 36 1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - MaximumrocknrollJune 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Monk, episode 141992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Option, 1993-97 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Pulse, Nov 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Puncture, 28, 30, 34, 40, 42, 1993-98 (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
    - Rockrgrl, Mar/Apr 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Rude International, Vol. 1, Issue 21998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Select, Jan, May, Jul 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
    - Spin, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Tuba Frenzy, Issue 3, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Warp, skatesnowsurfsound, Vol. 4. 3, Apr 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - W.F.M.U. LCD (Lowest Common Denominator) Program Guide, 1993-96 (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
    - The Wire, Issue 114, Aug 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Yak'uz'a, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Women's magazines
    - Barbie Bazaar, Jun 2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Curve, the Lesbian Magazine, Sep 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - IT Magazine (Irish Tatler), Aug 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Ms., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Sassy, 1991-93 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Seventeen, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Women's Options, a Village Voice Reference Directory, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - Kill Rock Stars
    - Vinyl disc releases, 7"
      - Woodcore series (spoken word)
        - Volume 1, "Rock Star" b/w "Mean," Kathleen Hanna and Slim Moon, 1991, 1993 Volume 2, Stacey Levine and Peter Toliver (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Volume 3, Jean Smith, "Carbon Angel," 1992
        - Volume 4, Penny Arcade, "A Cunt is a Useful Thing!" 1992
        - Volume 5, Juliana Luecking, "She's Good People," 1992
        - Volume 6, Peter Plate, "History Comes Around Like Snipers on a Rooftop," 1993
        - Volume 7, Exene Cervenka, "Tombs/ Woman of the Year/Rage," 1994
      - Bikini Kill, "New Radio, Rebel Girl, Demirep," 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Blood on the Saddle, 1994
      - The Cupid Car Club, M.P., "Werewolves," undated
      - Frumpies, "Babies and Bunnies,"undated
      - Godhead Silo, "Thee Friendship Villiage e.p.," 1993
      - Heavens to Betsy, "These Monsters are Real," circa 1992-93 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Karp, "I'm Done/Blublud," 1993
      - Mary Lou Lord, "Some Jingle Jangle Morning (When I'm Straight)/Western Union Desperate," 1993
      - Mukilteo Fairies, "Special Rites," 1994
      - The PeeChees, "Cup of Glory," undated
      - Phranc, "Bulldagger Swagger/Hillary's Eyebrows," 1994
      - Starpower, "Stargirl/Treefort," 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Team Dresch, 1994
      - Unwound
        - "Caterpillar/Miserific Condition/Love and Fear," 1991
        - "Kandy Korn Rituals/Against/Hating in D," 1992
        - "Mkultra/Totality," 1993
      - Witchypoo
        - "Groaning Machine/ You Belong to Me/Love Power," 1991 and hand silkscreened limited edition copy (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - "Mixed Metaphor," 1992-94
    - Vinyl disc releases, 10"
      - Huggy Bear, "Taking the Rough With the Smooch," 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Compact disc releases, 1991-94
      - Compilations (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - "Kill Rock Stars,"
        - "A Slice of Lemon"
        - "Rock Stars Kill"
        - "Stars Kill Rock"
      - Bikini Kill (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - "The C.D. version of the First Two Records,"
        - "Pussy Whisper"
      - Bratmobile
        - "Pottymouth," 1992
        - "The Real Janelle," undated
      - Godhead Silo, "The Scientific Supercake L.P.," 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Huggybear, "Weaponry Listens to Love," 1994
      - Julianna Luecking, "Big Broad," undated
      - Unwound (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - "Fake Train," 1993
        - "New Plastic Ideas," 1994
    - Audiocassette releases, 1991-94
      - Bikini Kill, "The Tape Version of the First Two Records" (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Bratmobile, "Pottymouth"
      - Sue P. Fox, "Light a Match Spark a Life," undated
  - Villa Villakula
    - Vinyl disc releases, 7"
      - Dame Darcy, "Will o' the Wisp/The Octopus," 1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Fresh Fish, "Pork Chop/Gossip," 1998
      - The Pendulum Floors, "Whatever Happened to…," 1996
      - Ruby Falls, "The Spirit is Willing/Dusty," undated [2 copies]
      - Sleater-Kinney, "You Ain't It," 1994 [2 copies] (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Stargirl e.p., 1996
      - "Un Cuerpo Exquisito," 1996
      - Victory at Sea, "Snow/Distorted," 1996
    - Vinyl disc releases, 10": Villa Villakula: Sleater-Kinney, "Sleater-Kinney," 1995 [2 copies] (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Vinyl disc releases, 12": compilation "Move into Villa Villakula," 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Compact disc releases, 1994-97
      - Bonfire Madigan, "…from the Burnpile," 1998 [2 copies] (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - "Move Into Villa Villakula," 1996 [3 copies]
      - The Pendulum Floors, "A Kicking Good Time with the Pendulum Floors," 1997 Un Cuerpo Exquisito, "Universidad de Culos Expertos," n.d. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Victory at Sea, "Easier Than Living," 1997
    - Vinyl disc distribution, 7"
      - Bloodletter, "on the rim/Get me," Reproductive Records, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Chickita, "Karen Learns About Our Nation," 100% Breakfast Records, undated Kudgel and The Swirlies, Cinder Block Records and Nervous Records, 1992 [cover art design and printing by Tinuviel]
      - Longstocking, "Equator/The Lonely Grasseater/Why," chou-chou records, 1996
      - Madigan, "Madigan Plays With Herself," Moon Puss Records, 1995 Masturbating Twat compilation, Fistful Records, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Ruby Falls, "Hysteria," 1993/ "Café No Problem," Silver Girl Records, 1994
      - Syrup usa, Tru-Luv Recordings
        - "Teen Death/Mysterious Dog, 1995
        - "Joie de Vol/Bulldozer," 1995
      - The Teensy Weensy Operator, La Brea, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Tizzy
        - "New Jersey/Betty vs. Veronica," Chunk Records, 1994
        - "Wives Should be Kissed…and Not Heard/Igloo," Pop Narcotic Recording Co., undated
    - Vinyl disc distribution, 12"
      - Ruby Falls, "Heroines," 1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Madigan, "Rock Stop," 1996
      - Victory at Sea, "Easier than Living," 1997
    - Compact disc distribution, 1993-96
      - Cheesecake, "You're Soaking In It," Girlie Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Dominatrix, "Self Delight," Clorine Records/Teenager in a Box, undated
      - Dragster, Hoppel Di Hoy Records, 1996
      - Jane Hohenberger's Spook Engine, Bloodlink Records, 1996
      - Madigan, "Rock Stop," Moon Puss Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Ninety-Nine, Endearing Records/Patsy Records, 1996
      - Ruby Falls, "Heroines," Silver Girl Records, 1996
      - Sleater-Kinney, Chainsaw Records, 1995
      - Tattle Tale, "Sew True," St. Francis Records, 1995
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND WRITINGS
    - Record and show reviews by Tinúviel in Middle East Monthly, Cambridge, MA, 1994-95 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
    - Letter from Alison Wolfe, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - SERIES III. RECORD LABELS
    - Kill Rock Stars
      - News clippings and reviews, 1991-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Flyers, posters, art, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Artwork for albums, posters, flyers, etc.
        - Miscellaneous, 1991-93 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - "Kill Rock Stars" compilation album, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - "Stars Kill Rock," artwork and related correspondence, 1992-93 (Box 14, Folder 7)
        - "Rock Stars Kill," layout and artwork, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - Mary Lou Lord, "Some Jingle Jangle Morning," 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - "Bikini Kill (R.I.P.)," Kaostica 3, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - "Josephine Was a Diva": zine by Jen Smith, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Villa Villakula
      - Notes about releases, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - News clippings
        - General, 1994-99 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - Sleater-Kinney, 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Posters, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - T-shirt: Bonfire Madigan, "…from the Burnpile," (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
    - News clippings, 1991-97 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Goldmine Magazine, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bad Attitude, Radical Women's Newspaper, London, 1993-94 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Kill Rock Stars and Villa Villakula artwork: carved linoleum blocks and miscellaneous,undated
  - News article about Kill Rock Stars in Error: The Official Newspaper of Vermiform Records 1994 (Map-case Flat file dwr 2)
  - Kill Rock Stars mail order catalogue, undated (Map-case Flat file dwr 2)
  - Tattletale "Sew True" poster; Kaia full length debut album poster, undated (Map-case Flat file dwr 2)